joeterceira.com 2014-11-12

# Privacy Policy JoeTerceira.com

### Privacy Policy

* * *

Updated: September 01, 2014

#### THE PRIVACY CODE OF THE CANADIAN REAL ESTATE ASSOCIATION

  * (I am a / We are) member(s) of The Canadian Real Estate Association (CREA) and adhere to and abide by the principles set out in the CREA Privacy Code. All employees and sales representatives associated with ( my / our office) sign an acknowledgement that they will comply with the requirements of the Code

#### PRIVACY POLICY

  * We only collect personal information necessary to effectively market and sell the property of sellers, to locate, assess and qualify properties for buyers and to otherwise provide professional and competent real estate services to clients and customers.

www.JoeTerceira.com is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read the Online Privacy Statement regarding the privacy practices of our website found on www.JoeTerceira.com. Please note that this statement applies only to the collection and use of information obtained online and not to data gathered offline. By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy. When you visit our website, expect to be notified of the following:

  * The collection and use of identifiable personal information;
  * Information sharing and choices regarding the collection, use, and distribution of personal information;
  * Online privacy protection for children;
  * How we protect personal information;
  * Links to other sites;
  * Notice of amendments;
  * Contacting us regarding personal information and privacy concerns.

#### WEBSITE LOGGING AND “COOKIES”

The company owns the information collected at several different points on our website. We do not sell, share or rent to other parties for ways or purposes not disclosed in this statement. The company collects personal and non-personal information in order to provide you our services including the access to the website’s newsletter. Below are the types of information we collect and their description.

  1. Personal and demographic information. Details that can help us identify you may include name, address, telephone number, or email address.
  2. Cookies. These are small text data that enable you to sign in to our services and allow us to enhance your online experience. Commonly stored on your hard disk drive, these are records of your preferences and other data on your computer so as to save time by eliminating the need of repeatedly providing the same information during later visits. They cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. The use of the cookie does not link to any identifiable personal information while on our site. You may reject their use but your experience may be limited in some areas of our site. Our business partners including advertisers may also use cookies on our site. We have no access or control over such cookies.
  3. Log files. These are IP addresses that help us administer the site, evaluate trends, track user’s movement, and collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. They are not linked to identifiable personal information.

#### COMMUNICATION

The company shares aggregated demographic information with partners and advertisers. This type of anonymous data is collected for purposes of studying a group or category of services or users. The information is not linked to any personal data that can be identified with any individual person.

We work with other parties to assist us and provide specific services and during these instances, we share name and contact details that are necessary for service provision. Our partners are not allowed to use identifiable personal information in any way other than the purpose of providing our listed services. Non-personal and identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We may release identifiable personal information in compliance with the law to enforce our site policies or to protect our, your and others rights, property or safety.

#### SECURITY

In compliance with the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, the company does not knowingly intend to collect information from individuals 13 years of age or younger.

#### YOUR RIGHT

The company maintains at all times administrative, technical, and physical safety measures to protect identifiable personal information from loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

#### LINKING

Our website contains links to other sites for convenience and information. Our company is not responsible for the privacy policies in these sites. We advise that you review the privacy notices for the use of such sites.

#### NOTIFICATION

Please note that www.JoeTerceira.com may change this privacy policy without notice, such that the effect of the amendment shall be effective immediately upon the posting of the modified agreement on the Site. Your continued access of this site shall be deemed a conclusive acceptance of the amended agreement.

#### CONTACT US

Should you feel the company is not abiding by its declared privacy policy, please contact us.
